[{"answer": "Well, that's right, Piers.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "What can you tell me?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "Piers, we've been watching as sheriff's deputies, as firefighters, as police officials, as investigators, as they've lined right -- walked past us into in this area where crews continue to search for victims.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "George, what can you tell me?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "It's nothing that your mind can really prepare you for.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "James, if you could tell us what's it like?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes, sir, going through the night.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Going through the night?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, you know the same thing that everybody else is out here.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What are they dealing with?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "George Howell, for now, thank you very much indeed.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "First off, it's Ms., but that's fine.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What can you tell me?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I can tell you that we will keep going all night long and, of course, all day tomorrow in a search and rescue mode and that we have a pretty strong network of people here in Oklahoma, who are -- I won't say used to this kind of weather, because you never get used to this type of destruction -- but we have lived with it and we know how to deal with it, and we know that we're not going to stop until we find every single person who's missing.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "But in terms of the outlying areas, how confident are you that you've gotten to all the people who may have been either killed or seriously hurt here?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "To be honest, I do expect it to go up.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "I mean, are you expecting the death toll to rise significantly from the current 51?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Piers, survivors and their families describing (inaudible) on CNN earlier, describing this as a nightmare, a bad dream, you know, just waiting to wake up, walking around like zombies, as if what has just unfolded, you know, isn't real.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What's happened in the last few hours?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "It's not clear.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Is it getting worse in terms of storm damage and power?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "It's been a busy couple nights.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Doctor, thank you for joining me, what can you tell me?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "We had 45 children that were taken to our children's hospital.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "I don't know; about 20 miles.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "And from what you saw in terms of the devastation that it wrought, how far, how wide an area -- we're hearing as many as 20 miles, maybe further -- were affected here?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Piers, that's a really good question.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "How does this rank in terms of scale and size?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Well, we're actually involved with ensuring that people have a safe place to stay the night.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Are you still finding people alive?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "You know, it is so early on with this just happening this afternoon.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Do you have any idea of how many people have been displaced?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "This one seems way more powerful.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "And in terms, Mr. Stephens, of the comparison between the two big tornadoes that you have survived, is this one to you, did it seem a lot bigger, a lot more powerful?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Well, climate change, you just have to think of it.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "As a scientist, when you hear about the size, scale, power and devastation of this tornado, what does it tell you about the ongoing debate about climate change?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "It brings back some haunting memories of May of '99, when we had a similar event and our church family kind of was involved in the same way.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What is your reaction to what has happened in Moore today?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I can confirm the 51.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yes, sir, actually I am.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "And are you expecting the toll to rise significantly higher than that still?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Have you any idea at the moment how many people in the end could have lost their lives?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "But just to clarify, 51 have been confirmed dead and you believe 40 more bodies have been recovered?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Well, actually, we just become involved when the person passes away, so we're not involved in the rescue unit or the rescue effort.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "In terms of the rescue operation at the Plaza Towers school, can you tell me anything about where you are with that?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Yes, sir, that's correct.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "So you're only notified when people are confirmed as having lost their lives?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130520pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "And you're now telling us that 40 more bodies have been recovered?", "qSentId": 462}]